Ankit Kasera

Assistant Manager

+91 7754837779



ankitkasera50@gmail.com

SUMMARY

I am a qualified and professional in sales, with 8 years of experience and good network in market. An effective communicator with excellent relationship building & interpersonal skills.

Strong analytical, problem solving & organizational abilities.

Experience in Business Development, Sales, Sales Strategic, Planning & Management And Experience of hanfling channel partners.

Presently associated with Merino Industries Ltd., Lucknow as Assistant Manager.

CAREER

JULY 2021 - PRESENT MERINO INDUSTRIES LIMITED

Company profile - Merino Laminates is one of the largest laminate sheet manufacturer and supplier for HPL, Special laminates, Compacts, Panels, External Wall Claddings etc.

- Regular interaction with the Developer, interior designers, architects, interior contractor etc.
- Coordination with every channel partner sales team & company team for joint work and Sales.
- Manage and maintain oem relationship.
- Providing Pre & after sales services to the esteemed clients.
- Dealing with Builders, Contractor, Architects in lucknow & surrounding area for support to specify our product in upcoming projects.
- Survey & analysis of market for sales.
- Specification in Lucknow Airport, Hotel Meghalay Inn & supplying in Medanta hospital, add 45+ oem & 40+ interior designer

JUNE 2019 - JUNE 2021 CERA SANITARYWARE LIMITED

Company profile - Cera sanitaryware India's fastest growing and largest manufacturing company in the sanitaryware. Keeping the needs of the modern customer in mind, like water-saving twin-flush coupled WCs, 4-litre flush WCs, and one-piece WCs.

- Engage with new and existing channel partners to set, achieve and exceed sales targets by developing and executing annual sales plans.
- Extension dealer network & open 5 new dealers in Lucknow, Gonda, Balrampur & Barabanki.
- To meet architects, contractor and project manager on regular basis for generating business from projects.
- Open 12 authorized retailer in Lucknow & 1 Sitapur as Cera Style Center, Working with 200 + retailers billing through dealers.

JUNE 2016 - JUNE 2019 SIMPOLO CERAMICS

Company profile - Simpolo ceramics, is the fastest growing company in sanitaryware manufacturer and supplier for sanitaryware, tiles, pvc cistern etc.

- Handling east uttarpradesh while being based at lucknow, developed market & expend dealer network.
- Developed Market in East U.P. area (Banda, Akbarpur, Faizabad, Gorakhpur, Azamgarh, Sultanpur, Ballia.
- Motivating and working with the channel partner's team to generate the sales and better coordination.
- Resolving Clients' queries & Problems, survey & analysis of market.
- Providing Pre & after sales services to the esteemed clients.
- Focus on Cost reduction and process improvement.
- Importance of gaining a clear understanding of dealer's Interest and his requirements.

AUGUST 2014 - MAY 2016 A.M.J. SALES PVT. LTD

- Developed a strong Sub Dealer and Dealers in the Lucknow.
- Open 3 Dealers & 35 Retailers.
- Responsibilities for all type of Tiles & Sanitary Ware Product sale only for Dealer.
- Supply Tiles, Sanitaryware & Faucets to Builders.

EDUCATION

2012 - 2014 LBSIMDS - LUCKNOW

Master of Business Administration in Marketing

2009 - 2012 MGKVP - VARANASI

Bachelor of Commerce

2009 RAJATHAN INTER COLLEGE - MIRZAPUR

Intermediate

2007 BASANT VIDYALAYA - MIRZAPUR

High School

PERSONAL DETAIL

- DATE OF BIRTH 20 October 1992
- LANGUAGES KNOWN Hindi & English
- ADDRESS House No 22, Raghuver Inclave, Faridi Nagar, Lucknow. U.P.